<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_304">
  <MasterPower>5c1e2577-5995-40a0-9b89-533372e84877</MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Void Terror</enUS>
    <frFR>Terreur du Vide</frFR>
    <zhTW>虛無恐獸</zhTW>
    <zhCN>虚空恐魔</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Ужасень Бездны</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Terror do Caos</ptBR>
    <plPL>Postrach Pustki</plPL>
    <koKR>공허의 괴물</koKR>
    <itIT>Terrore del Vuoto</itIT>
    <esMX>Terror del vacío</esMX>
    <esES>Terror del vacío</esES>
    <deDE>Schrecken der Leere</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="9" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Battlecry:&lt;/b&gt; Destroy the minions on either side of this minion and gain their Attack and Health.</enUS>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Cri de guerre :&lt;/b&gt; détruit les serviteurs adjacents et gagne leurs points d’Attaque et de Vie.</frFR>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;戰吼:&lt;/b&gt;摧毀其兩側的手下，獲得其攻擊力及生命值</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;战吼：&lt;/b&gt;消灭该随从两侧的随从，并获得他们的攻击力和生命值。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Боевой клич:&lt;/b&gt; уничтожает существа по обе стороны от себя и получает их атаку и здоровье.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Grito de Guerra:&lt;/b&gt; Destrua os lacaios dos dois lados deste e receba o Ataque e a Vida deles.</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Okrzyk bojowy:&lt;/b&gt; Zniszcz sąsiadujących z nim stronników, a zyska ich atak oraz zdrowie.</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;전투의 함성:&lt;/b&gt; 이 하수인 양옆에 있는 하수인들을 처치하고 그들의 공격력과 생명력을 얻습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Grido di Battaglia:&lt;/b&gt; distrugge i servitori adiacenti e ne ottiene l'Attacco e la Salute.</itIT>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla:&lt;/b&gt; destruye los esbirros que están a ambos lados de este esbirro y obtiene el Ataque y la Salud de los esbirros destruidos.</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla:&lt;/b&gt; Destruye a los esbirros adyacentes y obtiene su ataque y salud.</esES>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Kampfschrei:&lt;/b&gt; Vernichtet die benachbarten Diener und verleiht ihm deren Angriff und Leben.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="Race" enumID="200" type="Race" value="15" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Alex Horley Orlandelli</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>If you put this into your deck, you WILL lose the trust of your other minions.</enUS>
    <zhTW>如果你把這張放進套牌裡，你絕對會失去其他手下的信任。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>如果你把这张牌放到你的套牌中，你就会失去其他随从对你的信任。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Если вы положите эту карту в колоду, ваши существа перестанут вам доверять.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Se você colocar isso no seu deck, você VAI perder a confiança dos seus outros lacaios.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Jeśli włożysz tę kartę do talii, STRACISZ zaufanie wszystkich swoich stronników.</plPL>
    <koKR>이 카드를 덱에 넣으면 다른 하수인들의 신뢰를 잃습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Se lo aggiungerai al tuo mazzo, aspettati di perdere la fiducia degli altri tuoi servitori.</itIT>
    <frFR>Si vous l’ajoutez à votre deck, vous perdrez la confiance de vos autres serviteurs.</frFR>
    <esMX>Si pones esta carta en tu mazo, sin dudas PERDERÁS la confianza del resto de tus esbirros.</esMX>
    <esES>Si añades esto a tu mazo, perderás la confianza de tus otros esbirros.</esES>
    <deDE>Wenn er auftaucht, herrscht um ihn herum gähnende Leere.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Battlecry" enumID="218" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="5c1e2577-5995-40a0-9b89-533372e84877" />
</Entity>