<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_005">
  <MasterPower>41e81c66-edf9-4f0f-b7ba-9dad6a522133</MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Big Game Hunter</enUS>
    <frFR>La chasse au gros gibier</frFR>
    <zhTW>王牌獵人</zhTW>
    <zhCN>王牌猎人</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Опытный охотник</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Caçador Profissional</ptBR>
    <plPL>Łowca grubego zwierza</plPL>
    <koKR>나 이런 사냥꾼이야</koKR>
    <itIT>Esperto di Caccia Grossa</itIT>
    <esMX>Caza mayor</esMX>
    <esES>Cazador de fieras</esES>
    <deDE>Großwildjäger</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="4" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Battlecry:&lt;/b&gt; Destroy a minion with an Attack of 7 or more.</enUS>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Cri de guerre :&lt;/b&gt; détruit un serviteur avec 7 Attaque ou plus.</frFR>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;戰吼:&lt;/b&gt;摧毀一個攻擊力在7點以上的手下。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;战吼：&lt;/b&gt;消灭一个攻击力大于或等于7的随从。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Боевой клич:&lt;/b&gt; уничтожает существо с атакой 7 или больше.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Grito de Guerra:&lt;/b&gt; Destrua um lacaio com 7 ou mais de Ataque.</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Okrzyk bojowy:&lt;/b&gt; Zniszcz stronnika z atakiem 7 lub większym.</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;전투의 함성:&lt;/b&gt; 공격력 7 이상인 하수인을 1마리 처치합니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Grido di Battaglia:&lt;/b&gt; distrugge un servitore con Attacco pari a 7 o superiore.</itIT>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla:&lt;/b&gt; destruye un esbirro con 7 o más de Ataque.</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla&lt;/b&gt;: Destruye a un esbirro con 7 p. de ataque o más.</esES>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Kampfschrei:&lt;/b&gt; Vernichtet einen Diener mit mind. 7 Angriff.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="TargetingArrowText" enumID="325" type="String">
    <enUS>Destroy a minion with an Attack of 7 or more.</enUS>
    <frFR>Détruit un serviteur avec 7 Attaque ou plus.</frFR>
    <zhTW>摧毀一個攻擊力在7點以上的手下。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>消灭一个攻击力大于或等于7的随从。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Уничтожить существо с атакой 7 или больше</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Destrua um lacaio com 7 ou mais de Ataque.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Zniszcz stronnika z atakiem 7 lub większym.</plPL>
    <koKR>공격력 7 이상의 하수인 처치</koKR>
    <itIT>Distrugge un servitore con Attacco pari a 7 o superiore.</itIT>
    <esMX>Destruye a un esbirro con 7 de Ataque o más.</esMX>
    <esES>Destruye a un esbirro con 7 p. de ataque o más.</esES>
    <deDE>Vernichtet einen Diener mit mind. 7 Angriff.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Chris Seaman</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>Mere devilsaurs no longer excite him.  Soon he'll be trying to catch Onyxia with only a dull Krol Blade.</enUS>
    <zhTW>魔暴龍已經不再使他興奮。再沒多久，他就會開始嘗試用鈍掉的克羅之刃抓捕奧妮克希亞了。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>魔暴龙之类的猎物已经让他提不起兴趣了。很快，他就会提着一把生锈的“科罗尔之刃”去猎杀奥妮克希亚了。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Обычные дьявозавры больше его не вдохновляют. Скоро он будет пытаться поймать Ониксию, вооружившись лишь тупым клинком Крола.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Meros demossauros não o apetecem mais. Logo ele vai tentar capturar Onyxia apenas com uma Lâmina Krol cega.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Zwykłe diabłozaury przestały mu wystarczać. Wkrótce zapoluje na Onyksję korzystając jedynie ze snopowiązałki.</plPL>
    <koKR>그에게 데빌사우루스 따윈 코웃음만 나옵니다. 조만간 크롤 칼 하나 들고 오닉시아를 잡으러 간다더군요.</koKR>
    <itIT>Semplici gigantosauri non sono più stimolanti. Prova a cacciare Onyxia armato solo di un coltellino senza filo.</itIT>
    <frFR>Les simples diablosaures ne l’excitent même plus. Bientôt, il voudra attraper Onyxia avec une lame de Krol émoussée.</frFR>
    <esMX>Los simples demosaurios ya no lo apasionan. Pronto tratará de cazar a Onyxia con la sola ayuda de una hoja krol desafilada.</esMX>
    <esES>Los meros demosaurios ya no le interesan. Pronto intentará cazar a Onyxia sin más arma que una hoja Krol roma.</esES>
    <deDE>Das Jagen ordinärer Teufelssaurier reizt ihn nicht mehr so wie früher. Nicht mehr lange und er wird versuchen, Onyxia mit einer einfachen Krolklinge zur Strecke zu bringen.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Battlecry" enumID="218" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="41e81c66-edf9-4f0f-b7ba-9dad6a522133">
    <PlayRequirement reqID="22" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="1" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="41" param="7" />
  </Power>
</Entity>