<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="FP1_027">
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="12" />
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Stoneskin Gargoyle</enUS>
    <zhTW>石膚石像鬼</zhTW>
    <zhCN>岩肤石像鬼</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Каменная горгулья</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Gárgula Litopele</ptBR>
    <plPL>Kamiennoskóry gargulec</plPL>
    <koKR>돌가죽 가고일</koKR>
    <itIT>Gargoyle Pellepietrosa</itIT>
    <frFR>Gargouille peau-de-pierre</frFR>
    <esMX>Gárgola piel de piedra</esMX>
    <esES>Gárgola piel de piedra</esES>
    <deDE>Steinhautgargoyle</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="4" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>At the start of your turn, restore this minion to full Health.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在你的回合開始時，將這個手下的生命值恢復到全滿</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在你的回合开始时，为该随从恢复所有生命值。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Это существо полностью восстанавливает свое здоровье в начале каждого вашего хода.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>No início do seu turno, restaure toda a Vida deste lacaio.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Na początku swojej tury przywróć tego stronnika do pełni zdrowia.</plPL>
    <koKR>내 턴이 시작될 때, 이 하수인은 생명력을 모두 회복합니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>All'inizio del tuo turno, rigenera la sua Salute al massimo.</itIT>
    <frFR>Au début de votre tour, rend tous ses points de vie à ce serviteur.</frFR>
    <esMX>Al comienzo de tu turno, restaura toda la Salud de este esbirro.</esMX>
    <esES>Al comienzo de tu turno, restaura toda la salud de este esbirro.</esES>
    <deDE>Stellt zu Beginn Eures Zuges das volle Leben dieses Dieners wieder her.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>Stoneskin Gargoyles love freeze tag.</enUS>
    <zhTW>石膚石像鬼超愛捉迷藏的。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>岩肤石像鬼最喜欢玩的游戏就是：“我们都是木头人”。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Каменные горгульи очень любят играть в «Море волнуется раз».</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Gárgulas Litopele adoram brincar de estátua.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Gargulce, podobnie jak ożywione pomniki, nienawidzą gołębi.</plPL>
    <koKR>특기: 얼음땡</koKR>
    <itIT>I Gargoyle Pellepietrosa adorano giocare a "Un, due, tre, stella"!</itIT>
    <frFR>Quel est le jeu préféré des gargouilles peau-de-pierre ? 1, 2, 3, soleil !</frFR>
    <esMX>A los Gárgola piel de piedra les gusta jugar a la mancha estatua.</esMX>
    <esES>El juego favorito de las gárgolas es el escondite inglés.</esES>
    <deDE>Steinhautgargoyles gewinnen jede Partie Beamtenmikado.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Matt Smith</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisCard" enumID="364" type="String">
    <enUS>Unlocked by defeating Noth the Plaguebringer in the Plague Quarter.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在瘟疫區擊敗『瘟疫使者』諾斯後解鎖。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在击败瘟疫区的瘟疫使者诺斯后解锁。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Награда за победу над Нотом Чумным в Чумном квартале.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Desbloqueado ao derrotar Noth, o Pestífero, no Distrito da Peste.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Aby odblokować, pokonaj Nicza Siewcę Zarazy w Rewirze Zarazy.</plPL>
    <koKR>역병 지구의 역병술사 노스를 쓰러뜨려 잠금 해제</koKR>
    <itIT>Sbloccata sconfiggendo Noth l'Araldo della Piaga nell'Ala della Pestilenza.</itIT>
    <frFR>Obtenue en gagnant contre Noth le Porte-Peste dans le quartier de la Peste.</frFR>
    <esMX>Desbloqueada por derrotar a Noth el Pesteador en el Arrabal de la Peste.</esMX>
    <esES>Se desbloquea al derrotar a Noth el Pesteador en el Arrabal de la Peste.</esES>
    <deDE>Wird durch den Sieg über Noth den Seuchenfürsten im Seuchenviertel freigeschaltet.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisGoldCard" enumID="365" type="String">
    <enUS>Can be crafted after defeating Noth the Plaguebringer in the Plague Quarter.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在瘟疫區中擊敗『瘟疫使者』諾斯即可合成。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在瘟疫区击败瘟疫使者诺斯后能够制作。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Можно создать после победы над Нотом Чумным в Чумном квартале.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Pode ser criado após derrotar Noth, o Pestífero, no Distrito da Peste.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Można wykonać po pokonaniu Nicza Siewcy Zarazy w Rewirze Zarazy.</plPL>
    <koKR>역병 지구의 역병술사 노스를 쓰러뜨린 후 제작 가능</koKR>
    <itIT>Può essere creata dopo aver sconfitto Noth l'Araldo della Piaga nell'Ala della Pestilenza.</itIT>
    <frFR>Peut être créée après avoir battu Noth le Porte-Peste dans le quartier de la Peste.</frFR>
    <esMX>Se puede crear luego de derrotar a Noth el Pesteador en el Arrabal de la Peste.</esMX>
    <esES>Se puede crear tras derrotar a Noth el Pesteador en el Arrabal de la Peste.</esES>
    <deDE>Kann nach dem Sieg über Noth den Seuchenfürsten im Seuchenviertel hergestellt werden.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="TriggerVisual" enumID="32" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="6b426f96-31fb-448f-8538-c1c985bfb738" />
  <Power definition="5631f6ee-8065-45fb-80d1-5e121526af73" />
  <TriggeredPowerHistoryInfo effectIndex="0" showInHistory="False" />
</Entity>