<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_164">
  <MasterPower>
  </MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Nourish</enUS>
    <frFR>Nourrir</frFR>
    <zhTW>滋補術</zhTW>
    <zhCN>滋养</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Дар природы</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Nutrir</ptBR>
    <plPL>Nasycenie</plPL>
    <koKR>육성</koKR>
    <itIT>Nutrizione</itIT>
    <esMX>Nutrir</esMX>
    <esES>Nutrir</esES>
    <enGB>Nourish</enGB>
    <deDE>Pflege</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="5" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Choose One&lt;/b&gt; - Gain 2 Mana Crystals; or Draw 3 cards.</enUS>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Choix des armes :&lt;/b&gt; vous gagnez 2 cristaux de mana ou vous piochez 3 cartes.</frFR>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;二選一:&lt;/b&gt;獲得2個法力水晶，或抽3張牌。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;抉择&lt;/b&gt; - 获得2个法力水晶；或者抽3张牌。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Выберите эффект:&lt;/b&gt; вы получаете 2 кристалла маны; или вы берете 3 карты.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Escolha Um&lt;/b&gt; - Receba 2 Cristais de Mana; ou Compre 3 cards.</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Wybierz jedno:&lt;/b&gt; Otrzymujesz 2 kryształy many; lub dobierz 3 karty.</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;선택&lt;/b&gt; - 마나 수정을 둘 획득합니다. 또는 카드를 세 장 뽑습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Scegli:&lt;/b&gt; ottieni 2 Cristalli di Mana o pesca 3 carte.</itIT>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Elige una opción:&lt;/b&gt; obtén 2 Cristales de maná o roba 3 cartas.</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Elige una:&lt;/b&gt; Obtén 2 cristales de maná, o bien roba 3 cartas.</esES>
    <enGB>&lt;b&gt;Choose One&lt;/b&gt; - Gain 2 Mana Crystals; or Draw 3 cards.</enGB>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Wählt aus:&lt;/b&gt; Erhaltet 2 Manakristalle; oder zieht 3 Karten.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Terese Nielsen</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>Druids take nourishment from many things: the power of nature, the songbird's chirp, a chocolate cake.</enUS>
    <zhTW>德魯伊能透過許多東西攝取養分:自然之力、鳴禽之聲、巧克力蛋糕。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>德鲁伊能够从很多地方获得精神上的滋养：自然的伟力；鸟儿的鸣唱；蛋糕的美味。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Друиды черпают вдохновение во многих вещах: в силе природы, в пении птиц и в шоколадных тортиках.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Os druidas podem se nutrir de várias maneiras: com o poder da natureza, com o cantarolar das aves, com um bolo de chocolate.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Druidów syci wiele rzeczy: potęga natury, śpiew ptaków, tort czekoladowy.</plPL>
    <koKR>드루이드는 많은 것에서 힘을 얻습니다. 자연, 종달새의 지저귀는 소리, 초콜릿 케이크.</koKR>
    <itIT>I Druidi traggono nutrimento da molte cose: il potere della natura, il canto degli usignoli, le torte al cioccolato...</itIT>
    <frFR>Les druides se nourrissent de nombreuses choses : le pouvoir de la nature, le chant d’un oiseau, un gâteau au chocolat.</frFR>
    <esMX>Los druidas se nutren de distintas cosas: el poder de la naturaleza, el canto de las aves, un pastel de chocolate...</esMX>
    <esES>Los druidas se nutren de muchas cosas: el poder de la naturaleza... el canto de los pájaros... las tartas de chocolate...</esES>
    <enGB>Druids take nourishment from many things: the power of nature, the songbird's chirp, a chocolate cake.</enGB>
    <deDE>Druiden zehren ihre Kraft aus vielen Dingen: aus der Kraft der Natur, dem Zwitschern eines Singvogels oder einem Schokoladenkuchen.</deDE>
  </Tag>
</Entity>