<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_277">
  <MasterPower>
  </MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Arcane Missiles</enUS>
    <frFR>Projectiles des Arcanes</frFR>
    <zhTW>秘法飛彈</zhTW>
    <zhCN>奥术飞弹</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Чародейские стрелы</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Mísseis Arcanos</ptBR>
    <plPL>Tajemne pociski</plPL>
    <koKR>신비한 화살</koKR>
    <itIT>Missili Arcani</itIT>
    <esMX>Misiles arcanos</esMX>
    <esES>Misiles Arcanos</esES>
    <enGB>Arcane Missiles</enGB>
    <deDE>Arkane Geschosse</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="2" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="1" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>Shoot $3 missiles at random enemies for 1 damage each.</enUS>
    <frFR>Tire $3 projectiles sur des adversaires aléatoires, infligeant chacun 1 point de dégâts.</frFR>
    <zhTW>發射$3顆飛彈攻擊隨機的敵人，每一顆造成1點傷害。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>随机对敌人发射$3枚飞弹，每枚飞弹造成1点伤害。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Выстреливает в случайных персонажей противника магические заряды ($3), каждый из которых наносит 1 ед. урона.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Dispare $3 mísseis em inimigos aleatórios, causando 1 de dano a cada um deles.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Wystrzel $3 pociski w losowych wrogów, zadając każdemu 1 pkt. obrażeń.</plPL>
    <koKR>피해를 1 주는 화살 $3개를 무작위 적들에게 발사합니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Lancia $3 missili infliggendo 1 danno ciascuno a nemici casuali.</itIT>
    <esMX>Dispara $3 misiles a enemigos aleatorios que infligen 1 de daño cada uno.</esMX>
    <esES>Dispara $3 misiles a enemigos aleatorios. Cada uno inflige 1 p. de daño.</esES>
    <enGB>Shoot $3 missiles at random enemies for 1 damage each.</enGB>
    <deDE>Verschießt $3 Geschosse auf zufällige Feinde und verursacht jeweils 1 Schaden.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="DevState" enumID="268" type="DevState" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>You'd think you'd be able to control your missiles a little better since you're a powerful mage and all.</enUS>
    <zhTW>你本來以為你能更熟練地控制這些飛彈，畢竟你是個強大的法師，對吧。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>既然你想要做一个超级厉害的法师，就必须得把奥术飞弹控制得好一些。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Такому могущественному магу как ты наверняка хотелось бы лучше управлять своими чародейскими стрелами.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>E você que pensava que ficaria um pouco mais fácil controlar os mísseis, sendo um mago poderoso e tal.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Potężni magowie powinni chyba lepiej kontrolować swoje pociski, co nie?</plPL>
    <koKR>솔직히 당신은 엄청나게 강한 마법사니까 신비한 화살 정도는 잘 조준할 수 있을 거라 생각하셨죠?</koKR>
    <itIT>Visto che sei un Mago potentissimo, ci si aspetterebbe un po' di più da te sul controllo dei Missili Arcani.</itIT>
    <frFR>Vous devriez pouvoir contrôler vos missiles un peu mieux que ça puisque vous êtes un puissant mage et tout et tout.</frFR>
    <esMX>Un mago tan poderoso y con tanta experiencia como tú debería poder controlar un poco mejor sus misiles, ¿no te parece?</esMX>
    <esES>Para ser un mago tan poderoso, podrías controlar tus misiles un poco mejor.</esES>
    <enGB>You'd think you'd be able to control your missiles a little better since you're a powerful mage and all.</enGB>
    <deDE>Man möchte glauben, dass Ihr Eure Geschosse etwas besser kontrollieren könntet, nun da Ihr ein mächtiger Magier und so weiter seid.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Warren Mahy</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="ImmuneToSpellpower" enumID="349" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="72ca23c3-af5c-481b-aee8-e758e1ffbf27" />
</Entity>