<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="PRO_001">
  <MasterPower>3f0c00bd-9382-4ce6-b16f-bd009cc5e1ec</MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Elite Tauren Chieftain</enUS>
    <zhTW>精英牛頭大佬</zhTW>
    <zhCN>精英牛头人酋长</zhCN>
    <ruRU>E.T.C.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Chefe Tauren Elite</ptBR>
    <plPL>Elitarny Taureński Czempion</plPL>
    <koKR>정예 타우렌 족장</koKR>
    <itIT>Elite Tauren Chieftain</itIT>
    <frFR>Elite Tauren Chieftain</frFR>
    <esMX>Elite Tauren Chieftain</esMX>
    <esES>Elite Tauren Chieftain</esES>
    <deDE>Elite Tauren Chieftain</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="11" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="5" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="5" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Battlecry:&lt;/b&gt; Give both players the power to ROCK! (with a Power Chord card)</enUS>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;戰吼:&lt;/b&gt;賦予雙方玩家搖滾的能力!(一張強力和弦卡)</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;战吼：&lt;/b&gt;让两位玩家都具有摇滚的能力！（双方各获得一张强力和弦牌）</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Боевой клич:&lt;/b&gt; оба игрока получают силу РОКА! (а также одну из карт серии «Мощный аккорд»)</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Grito de Guerra:&lt;/b&gt; Dê aos dois jogadores o poder do ROCK! (com um card de Acorde Poderoso)</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Okrzyk bojowy:&lt;/b&gt; Daj obu graczom moc metalu! (oraz kartę „Odjazdowy riff”)</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;전투의 함성:&lt;/b&gt; 두 플레이어 모두 파워 코드 카드를 1장 뽑고 &lt;b&gt;로큰롤&lt;/b&gt;에 흠뻑 취합니다!</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Grido di Battaglia:&lt;/b&gt; fornisce il potere del ROCK a entrambi i giocatori!</itIT>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Cri de guerre :&lt;/b&gt; confère aux deux joueurs la puissance du ROCK ! (grâce à une carte au riff dément !)</frFR>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla:&lt;/b&gt; Otorga a ambos jugadores el poder del ROCK (con una carta Acorde Potente)</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla:&lt;/b&gt; ¡Otorga a ambos jugadores el poder del ROCK! (con una carta de acorde)</esES>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Kampfschrei:&lt;/b&gt; Verleiht beiden Spielern die Macht des ROCK! (durch eine Powerakkordkarte)</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisGoldCard" enumID="365" type="String">
    <enUS>Awarded at BlizzCon 2013.</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Samwise Didier</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Elite" enumID="114" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>He's looking for a drummer.  The current candidates are: Novice Engineer, Sen'jin Shieldmasta', and Ragnaros the Firelord.</enUS>
    <zhTW>他正在找鼓手。目前應徵的人有:見習工程師、森金禦盾大師和『炎魔』拉格納羅斯。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>他正在物色一名鼓手。目前的候选人包括：工程师学徒，森金持盾卫士，还有炎魔之王拉格纳罗斯。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Внимание! Группе требуется барабанщик! Текущие кандидаты: инженер-новичок, щитоносец Сен'джин и Рагнарос.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Ele está procurando um baterista. Os canditatos até agora são: Engenheira Novata, Mestre Escudeiro de Sen'jin e Ragnaros, o Senhor do Fogo.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Największe hity ETC to: „I Am a Murloc” (Jestem murlokiem), „Rogues Do It...” (Łotrzy robią to...) oraz „Power of the Horde” (Potęga Hordy).</plPL>
    <koKR>현재 드러머를 구하는 중입니다. 풋내기 기술자, 센진 방패대가, 불의 군주 라그나로스가 후보라네요.</koKR>
    <itIT>Sta cercando un batterista. Al momento i migliori candidati sono: Ingegnera Novizia, Guardiano di Sen'jin e soprattutto Ragnaros, il Signore del Fuoco.</itIT>
    <frFR>« Si je dois être détruit par le rock'n roll, je m’assurerai que le rock'n roll soit détruit en même temps que moi ! »</frFR>
    <esMX>Está buscando baterista. Sus candidatos son: Ingeniera novicia, Sen'jin Maestro de escudos y Ragnaros el Señor del Fuego.</esMX>
    <esES>¡Muuuuévete!</esES>
    <deDE>Schon als Kalb war er Fan von Muhtallica.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Battlecry" enumID="218" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="3f0c00bd-9382-4ce6-b16f-bd009cc5e1ec" />
  <EntourageCard cardID="PRO_001a" />
  <EntourageCard cardID="PRO_001b" />
  <EntourageCard cardID="PRO_001c" />
</Entity>