<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_334">
  <MasterPower>d2bacef2-8095-466f-9507-655c664f17b1</MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Shadow Madness</enUS>
    <frFR>Folie de l’ombre</frFR>
    <zhTW>暗影狂亂</zhTW>
    <zhCN>暗影狂乱</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Темное безумие</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Insanidade Sombria</ptBR>
    <plPL>Szaleństwo cieni</plPL>
    <koKR>암흑의 광기</koKR>
    <itIT>Follia d'Ombra</itIT>
    <esMX>Locura sombría</esMX>
    <esES>Demencia oscura</esES>
    <deDE>Dunkler Wahnsinn</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="6" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="4" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>Gain control of an enemy minion with 3 or less Attack until end of turn.</enUS>
    <frFR>Prend le contrôle d’un serviteur adverse avec 3 ATQ ou moins jusqu’à la fin du tour.</frFR>
    <zhTW>控制一個敵方攻擊力在3點以下的手下，直到回合結束。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>直到回合结束，获得一个攻击力小于或等于3的敌方随从的控制权。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Вы получаете контроль над существом противника с атакой 3 или меньше до конца хода.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Assuma o controle de um lacaio inimigo com 3 ou menos de Ataque até o final do turno.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Do końca tury przejmij kontrolę nad wrogim stronnikiem z atakiem 3 lub mniejszym.</plPL>
    <koKR>공격력 3 이하인 적 하수인 1마리를 이번 턴에만 조종합니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Prendi il controllo di un servitore nemico con Attacco pari a 3 o inferiore fino alla fine del turno.</itIT>
    <esMX>Toma el control de un esbirro enemigo con 3 de Ataque o menos hasta el final del turno.</esMX>
    <esES>Toma el control de un esbirro enemigo con 3 p. de ataque o menos hasta el final del turno.</esES>
    <deDE>Übernehmt bis zum Ende des Zuges die Kontrolle über einen feindlichen Diener mit max. 3 Angriff.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Mark Gibbons</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>You can rationalize it all you want, it's still a mean thing to do.</enUS>
    <zhTW>你要怎麼合理化解釋都行，不管怎麼說，這樣做還是很卑鄙。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>随你如何让它恢复理智，这个过程本身仍是件卑劣的事。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Можете оправдывать свой поступок чем угодно, но это все равно будет подлостью!</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Pode tentar racionalizar o quanto quiser, você é malvado por fazer isso.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Tłumacz to sobie jak chcesz, ale to dość wredne zagranie.</plPL>
    <koKR>당신이 뭐라고 변명하든, 상대편 입장에선 짜증납니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Puoi giustificarti quanto vuoi, ma è davvero una cosa brutta da fare.</itIT>
    <frFR>Vous pouvez vous justifier aussi longtemps que vous voulez, c’est quand même inqualifiable.</frFR>
    <esMX>Puedes dar todas las explicaciones que quieras, pero no deja de ser perverso.</esMX>
    <esES>¡Eso es jugar sucio! ¡Bien hecho!</esES>
    <deDE>Für den übernehmenden Spieler der helle Wahnsinn!</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Power definition="d2bacef2-8095-466f-9507-655c664f17b1">
    <PlayRequirement reqID="11" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="1" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="3" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="12" param="1" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="8" param="3" />
  </Power>
</Entity>