<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_350">
  <MasterPower>
  </MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Prophet Velen</enUS>
    <frFR>Prophète Velen</frFR>
    <zhTW>預言者費倫</zhTW>
    <zhCN>先知维纶</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Пророк Велен</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Profeta Velen</ptBR>
    <plPL>Prorok Velen</plPL>
    <koKR>예언자 벨렌</koKR>
    <itIT>Profeta Velen</itIT>
    <esMX>Profeta Velen</esMX>
    <esES>Profeta Velen</esES>
    <deDE>Prophet Velen</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="6" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="7" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="7" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="7" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>Double the damage and healing of your spells and Hero Power.</enUS>
    <frFR>Double les dégâts et les soins de vos sorts et de votre pouvoir héroïque.</frFR>
    <zhTW>使你的法術及英雄能力所造成的傷害和治療效果加倍。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>使你的法术牌和英雄技能的伤害和治疗效果翻倍。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Ваши заклинания и сила героя восстанавливают здоровье и наносят урон в двойном объеме.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Dobre o dano e a cura dos seus feitiços e Poder Heroico.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Podwajasz wartości obrażeń i leczenia z twoich zaklęć oraz mocy specjalnej.</plPL>
    <koKR>내 주문과 영웅 능력의 피해량과 치유량을 2배 증가시킵니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Raddoppia i danni e le cure delle tue Magie e del Potere Eroe.</itIT>
    <esMX>Duplica el daño y la sanación de tus hechizos y de tu Poder de héroe.</esMX>
    <esES>Duplica el daño y la sanación de tus hechizos y de tu poder de héroe.</esES>
    <deDE>Verdoppelt den Schaden und die Heilung Eurer Zauber und Heldenfähigkeiten.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Elite" enumID="114" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Wei Wang</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>He's been exiled from his home, and all his brothers turned evil, but otherwise he doesn't have a lot to complain about.</enUS>
    <zhTW>他呢，從家園被放逐，他的兄弟都變成壞人，至於其他倒是沒什麼好抱怨的了。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>他被逐出他的家园。他兄弟们都变成了邪恶的主宰......但是除此之外，他好像也没有什么别的可以抱怨的了。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Он был изгнан из родного дома, его братья обратились ко злу, но в остальном у него все хорошо!</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Ele foi exilado de casa e todos os seus irmãos ficaram maus, mas fora isso ele não tem do que reclamar.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Został wygnany z domu, a wszyscy jego bracia przeszli na stronę zła, ale poza tym nie ma na co narzekać.</plPL>
    <koKR>고향에서 추방당했고, 형제들은 사악하게 변했지만, 불만이 있는 것 같진 않네요.</koKR>
    <itIT>È stato esiliato dalla sua patria e tutti i suoi fratelli sono diventati crudeli. A parte questo, non ha molto di cui lamentarsi.</itIT>
    <frFR>Il a été banni, ses frères ont mal tourné, mais à part ça, il a vraiment tout pour être heureux.</frFR>
    <esMX>Lo exiliaron de su hogar y todos sus hermanos se volvieron malvados. Pero dejando eso de lado, no tiene mucho de qué quejarse.</esMX>
    <esES>Lo exiliaron de su hogar, sus hermanos se aliaron con demonios y lleva desde entonces de pie en El Exodar. Se merece la jubilación.</esES>
    <deDE>Er wurde aus seiner Heimat verbannt, alle seine Brüder sind verderbt, aber ansonsten geht es ihm eigentlich prima.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Power definition="c35ec869-7365-418e-8628-2234b9a7f1a6" />
</Entity>