<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_126">
  <MasterPower>ad566701-d43c-435a-8d70-9dd701274824</MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Betrayal</enUS>
    <frFR>Trahison</frFR>
    <zhTW>背叛</zhTW>
    <zhCN>背叛</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Предательство</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Traição</ptBR>
    <plPL>Zdrada</plPL>
    <koKR>배신</koKR>
    <itIT>Tradimento</itIT>
    <esMX>Traición</esMX>
    <esES>Traición</esES>
    <deDE>Verrat</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="7" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="6" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>An enemy minion deals its damage to the minions next to it.</enUS>
    <frFR>Un serviteur adverse inflige ses dégâts aux serviteurs à côté de lui.</frFR>
    <zhTW>一個敵方手下對它身旁的手下造成相當於其攻擊力的傷害。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>一个敌方随从对其相邻的随从造成等同于其攻击力的伤害。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Выбранное существо противника наносит урон, равный своей атаке, существам, находящимся по обе стороны от него.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Um lacaio inimigo causa dano aos lacaios ao lado dele.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Wrogi stronnik zadaje obrażenia innym stronnikom obok siebie.</plPL>
    <koKR>적 하수인이 자신의 공격력만큼 양옆의 하수인들에게 피해를 줍니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Un servitore nemico infligge danni pari al suo attacco ai servitori nemici adiacenti.</itIT>
    <esMX>Un esbirro enemigo inflige su daño a los esbirros adyacentes.</esMX>
    <esES>Un esbirro enemigo inflige su daño a los esbirros adyacentes.</esES>
    <deDE>Ein feindlicher Diener fügt benachbarten Dienern seinen Schaden zu.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="DevState" enumID="268" type="DevState" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Lucas Graciano</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>Everyone has a price. Gnomes, for example, can be persuaded by stuffed animals and small amounts of chocolate.</enUS>
    <zhTW>每個人都有一個價碼。以地精來說，他們可以被動物布娃娃跟些許的巧克力收買。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>每个人都有背叛的价码。拿侏儒打比方的话，塞满馅料的动物和一小点儿巧克力就能让他们就范。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>У каждого есть цена. Гномы, например, сделают что угодно за мягкую игрушку и плитку шоколада.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Todos têm um preço. Gnomos, por exemplos, podem ser persuadidos com bichos de pelúcia e pequenas quantidades de chocolate.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Każdy ma swoją cenę. Na przykład gnomy można przekupić pluszowymi zwierzątkami i niewielką ilością czekolady.</plPL>
    <koKR>모든 배신에는 대가가 필요합니다. 예를 들어 노움을 배신시키려면 동물 인형과 약간의 초콜릿이 필요하죠.</koKR>
    <itIT>Tutti hanno un prezzo. Gli Gnomi, per esempio, possono essere convinti con animali di pezza e un po' di cioccolato.</itIT>
    <frFR>Pourquoi trahir ? Je dirais que c’est probablement une réponse compulsive à une crainte de m’attacher.</frFR>
    <esMX>Todos tienen su precio. Los Gnomos, por ejemplo, hacen lo que sea por un oso de peluche y un poco de chocolate.</esMX>
    <esES>Te hará una oferta que no podrás rechazar.</esES>
    <deDE>Zu einem gewissen Preis ist sich halt jeder selbst der Nächste.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Power definition="ad566701-d43c-435a-8d70-9dd701274824">
    <PlayRequirement reqID="11" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="1" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="3" param="" />
  </Power>
</Entity>