<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_559">
  <MasterPower>
  </MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Archmage Antonidas</enUS>
    <frFR>Archimage Antonidas</frFR>
    <zhTW>大法師安東尼達斯</zhTW>
    <zhCN>大法师安东尼达斯</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Архимаг Антонидас</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Arquimago Antônidas</ptBR>
    <plPL>Arcymag Antonidas</plPL>
    <koKR>대마법사 안토니다스</koKR>
    <itIT>Arcimago Antonidas</itIT>
    <esMX>Archimago Antonidas</esMX>
    <esES>Archimago Antonidas</esES>
    <enGB>Archmage Antonidas</enGB>
    <deDE>Erzmagier Antonidas</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="5" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="7" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="7" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>Whenever you cast a spell, put a 'Fireball' spell into your hand.</enUS>
    <frFR>Chaque fois que vous lancez un sort, place un sort « boule de feu » dans votre main.</frFR>
    <zhTW>每當你施放法術，你的手牌便多一張「火球術」。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>每当你施放一个法术时，将一张“火球术”法术牌置入你的手牌。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Каждый раз, когда вы разыгрываете карту заклинания, вы кладете карту «Огненный шар» к себе в руку.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Sempre que você lançar um feitiço, coloque um feitiço "Bola de Fogo" na sua mão.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Za każdym razem kiedy rzucasz zaklęcie, weź do ręki zaklęcie „Kula ognia”.</plPL>
    <koKR>당신이 주문을 시전할 때마다 '화염구' 주문을 손으로 가져옵니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Ogni volta che lanci una Magia, ottieni una carta Palla di Fuoco.</itIT>
    <esMX>Cada vez que lanzas un hechizo, pon un hechizo "Bola de Fuego" en tu mano.</esMX>
    <esES>Cada vez que lanzas un hechizo, coloca un hechizo "Bola de Fuego" en tu mano.</esES>
    <enGB>Whenever you cast a spell, put a 'Fireball' spell into your hand.</enGB>
    <deDE>Erhaltet jedes Mal einen „Feuerball“-Zauber auf Eure Hand, wenn Ihr einen Zauber wirkt.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="4" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInPlay" enumID="252" type="String">
    <enUS>Grand Magus</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Elite" enumID="114" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>Antonidas was the Grand Magus of the Kirin Tor, and Jaina's mentor.  This was a big step up from being Grand Magus of Jelly Donuts.</enUS>
    <zhTW>安東尼達斯生前是祈倫托的大魔導師，也是珍娜的導師。這比果凍甜甜圈的大魔導師高尚多了。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>肯瑞托的首席法师，达拉然最伟大的子民，安东尼达斯在被巫妖王阿尔萨斯杀死之前，曾是吉安娜的导师。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Антонидас был великим магом Кирин-Тора и учителем Джайны. После предыдущей работы великим зачаровывателем пончиков с джемом это было серьезное повышение.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Antônidas foi o Grão-mago do Kirin Tor e mentor de Jaina. Foi um enorme passo desde seu tempo como Grão-mago das Jujubas.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Antonidas był Wielkim Magiem Kirin Toru oraz mentorem Jainy. To znaczny awans w porównaniu z Wielkim Magiem Domowych Babeczek.</plPL>
    <koKR>안토니다스는 키린 토의 대학자이자 제이나의 스승이었습니다. 젤리 도넛의 대학자였던 그로선 장족의 발전이라할 수 있죠.</koKR>
    <itIT>Antonidas era il Gran Magus del Kirin Tor e il mentore di Jaina. Prima era solo il Gran Magus delle Ciambelle alla Crema.</itIT>
    <frFR>Antonidas était le grand magus du Kirin Tor et le mentor de Jaina. C’était une sacrée ascension sociale par rapport à l’époque où les gens l’appelaient le faux mage blanc.</frFR>
    <esMX>Antes de llegar a ser el Gran mago de los Kirin Tor y el mentor de Jaina, Antonidas era mejor conocido como el Gran mago de los bizcochos.</esMX>
    <esES>Antonidas fue el gran mago del Kirin Tor, y el mentor de Jaina. Todo esto antes de convertirse en monumento conmemorativo.</esES>
    <enGB>Antonidas was the Grand Magus of the Kirin Tor, and Jaina's mentor.  This was a big step up from being Grand Magus of Jelly Donuts.</enGB>
    <deDE>Der Großmagus der Kirin Tor und Dalarans großartigster Sohn. Selbst Zwerge beneideten ihn um seinen Bart.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Wayne Reynolds</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="TriggerVisual" enumID="32" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="11c61eb0-e38e-42e2-9240-706392b332a6" />
  <TriggeredPowerHistoryInfo effectIndex="0" showInHistory="False" />
</Entity>