<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="FP1_009">
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Deathlord</enUS>
    <zhTW>死亡領主</zhTW>
    <zhCN>死亡领主</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Владыка Смерти</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Necrolorde</ptBR>
    <plPL>Pan Śmierci</plPL>
    <koKR>죽음의 군주</koKR>
    <itIT>Signore della Morte</itIT>
    <frFR>Seigneur de la mort</frFR>
    <esMX>Señor de la muerte</esMX>
    <esES>Señor de la Muerte</esES>
    <deDE>Todesfürst</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="12" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="8" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Taunt. Deathrattle:&lt;/b&gt; Your opponent puts a minion from their deck into the battlefield.</enUS>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;嘲諷。死亡之聲:&lt;/b&gt;你的對手將牌堆中的一個手下放進戰場</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;嘲讽，亡语：&lt;/b&gt;你的对手将一个随从从其牌库置入战场。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Провокация. Предсмертный хрип:&lt;/b&gt; ваш противник кладет существо из своей колоды на поле боя.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Provocar. Último Suspiro:&lt;/b&gt; Seu oponente coloca um lacaio do próprio deck no campo de batalha.</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Prowokacja&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;b&gt;Agonia:&lt;/b&gt; Twój przeciwnik umieszcza losowego stronnika ze swojej talii na polu bitwy.</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;도발. 죽음의 메아리:&lt;/b&gt; 상대편이 덱에 있는 하수인 하나를 전장에 놓습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Provocazione&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;b&gt;Rantolo di Morte:&lt;/b&gt; l'avversario mette sul campo di battaglia un servitore casuale dal suo mazzo.</itIT>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Provocation. Râle d’agonie :&lt;/b&gt; votre adversaire place un serviteur de son deck sur le champ de bataille.</frFR>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Provocación. Estertor:&lt;/b&gt; tu adversario pone un esbirro de su mazo en el campo de batalla.</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Provocar. Último aliento:&lt;/b&gt; Tu oponente coloca un esbirro de su mazo en el campo de batalla.</esES>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Spott. Todesröcheln:&lt;/b&gt; Euer Gegner legt einen Diener aus seinem Deck auf das Schlachtfeld.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Ben Olson</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisCard" enumID="364" type="String">
    <enUS>Unlocked by defeating The Four Horsemen in the Military Quarter.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在軍事區擊敗四騎士後解鎖。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在击败军事区的天启四骑士后解锁。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Награда за победу над четырьмя всадниками в Военном квартале.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Desbloqueado ao derrotar Os Quatro Cavaleiros no Distrito Militar.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Aby odblokować, pokonaj Czterech Jeźdźców w Rewirze Zbrojnych.</plPL>
    <koKR>군사 지구의 4인 기사단을 쓰러뜨려 잠금 해제</koKR>
    <itIT>Sbloccata sconfiggendo i Cavalieri dell'Apocalisse nell'Ala dei Combattenti.</itIT>
    <frFR>Obtenue en gagnant contre les quatre cavaliers dans le quartier Militaire.</frFR>
    <esMX>Desbloqueada por derrotar a Los cuatro jinetes en el Arrabal Militar.</esMX>
    <esES>Se desbloquea al derrotar a Los Cuatro Jinetes en el Arrabal Militar.</esES>
    <deDE>Wird durch den Sieg über die vier Reiter im Militärviertel freigeschaltet.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>"Rise from your grave!" - Kel'Thuzad</enUS>
    <zhTW>「從墳墓中起身吧!」-科爾蘇加德</zhTW>
    <zhCN>“从你的坟墓中醒来吧！”——克尔苏加德</zhCN>
    <ruRU>«Восстаньте из могил!» — Кел'Тузад</ruRU>
    <ptBR>"Erga-se de sua tumba!" — Kel'thuzad</ptBR>
    <plPL>„Powstańcie z grobów! Tylko bez mikrobów!” - Kel'Thuzad</plPL>
    <koKR>"무덤에서 일어나라!" - 켈투자드</koKR>
    <itIT>"Risorgi dalla fossa!" - Kel'Thuzad</itIT>
    <frFR>« Lève-toi de ta tombe ! » - Kel’Thuzad</frFR>
    <esMX>"¡Levántate de tu tumba!" —Kel'Thuzad</esMX>
    <esES>"¡Álzate de la tumba!". - Kel'Thuzad</esES>
    <deDE>„Erhebt Euch aus Eurem Grab!“ – Kel'Thuzad</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisGoldCard" enumID="365" type="String">
    <enUS>Can be crafted after defeating The Four Horsemen in the Military Quarter.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在軍事區中擊敗四騎士即可合成。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在军事区击败天启四骑士后能够制作。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Можно создать после победы над четырьмя всадниками в Военном квартале.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Pode ser criado após derrotar Os Quatro Cavaleiros no Distrito Militar.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Można wykonać po pokonaniu Czterech Jeźdźców w Rewirze Zbrojnych.</plPL>
    <koKR>군사 지구의 4인 기사단을 쓰러뜨린 후 제작 가능</koKR>
    <itIT>Può essere creata dopo aver sconfitto i Cavalieri dell'Apocalisse nell'Ala dei Combattenti.</itIT>
    <frFR>Peut être créée après avoir battu les quatre cavaliers dans le quartier Militaire.</frFR>
    <esMX>Se puede crear luego de derrotar a Los cuatro jinetes en el Arrabal Militar.</esMX>
    <esES>Se puede crear tras derrotar a Los Cuatro Jinetes en el Arrabal Militar.</esES>
    <deDE>Kann nach dem Sieg über die vier Reiter im Militärviertel hergestellt werden.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Taunt" enumID="190" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Deathrattle" enumID="217" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <ReferencedTag name="Deathrattle" enumID="217" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="95d16465-9c51-426a-81a4-21bb499bd217" />
  <Power definition="481a5bd9-4b2a-42a5-a378-4cd6c583d8b9" />
  <TriggeredPowerHistoryInfo effectIndex="0" showInHistory="False" />
</Entity>