<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_613">
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Edwin VanCleef</enUS>
    <frFR>Edwin VanCleef</frFR>
    <zhTW>艾德溫·范克里夫</zhTW>
    <zhCN>艾德温·范克里夫</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Эдвин ван Клиф</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Edwin VanCleef</ptBR>
    <plPL>Edwin VanCleef</plPL>
    <koKR>에드윈 밴클리프</koKR>
    <itIT>Edwin VanCleef</itIT>
    <esMX>Edwin VanCleef</esMX>
    <esES>Edwin VanCleef</esES>
    <deDE>Edwin van Cleef</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="5" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Class" enumID="199" type="Class" value="7" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="6" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Combo:&lt;/b&gt; Gain +2/+2 for each card played earlier this turn.</enUS>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Combo :&lt;/b&gt; gagne +2/+2 pour chaque carte jouée auparavant pendant ce tour.</frFR>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;連擊:&lt;/b&gt;在本回合中，之前所打出的每一張牌，都使其獲得+2/+2</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;连击：&lt;/b&gt;在本回合中，使用此牌前每打出一张其他牌，便获得+2/+2。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Серия приемов:&lt;/b&gt; это существо получает +2/+2 за каждую другую карту, разыгранную ранее на этом ходу.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Combo:&lt;/b&gt; Receba +2/+2 para cada um dos cards jogados antes neste turno.</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Kombinacja:&lt;/b&gt; Otrzymuje +2/+2 za każdą kartę zagraną wcześniej w tej turze.</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;연계:&lt;/b&gt; 이번 턴에 앞서 낸 카드 1장당 +2/+2를 얻습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Combo:&lt;/b&gt; ottiene +2/+2 per ogni carta giocata precedentemente in questo turno.</itIT>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Combo:&lt;/b&gt; obtiene +2/+2 por cada carta que se haya jugado antes en este turno.</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Combo:&lt;/b&gt; Obtiene +2/+2 por cada carta que se haya jugado en este turno.</esES>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Combo:&lt;/b&gt; Erhält für jede in diesem Zug bereits gespielte Karte +2/+2.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Elite" enumID="114" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Jesper Ejsing</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>He led the Stonemasons in the reconstruction of Stormwind, and when the nobles refused to pay, he founded the Defias Brotherhood to, well, &lt;i&gt;deconstruct&lt;/i&gt; Stormwind.</enUS>
    <zhTW>他帶領石匠協會重建暴風城。當貴族們拒絕付賬後，他成立了迪菲亞兄弟會來，嗯，&lt;b&gt;拆除&lt;/b&gt;暴風城。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>他领导石匠协会重建了暴风城，而当贵族们拒绝支付工钱的时候，他将领导迪菲亚兄弟会，嗯，拆掉暴风城。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Он возглавлял братство Каменщиков, помогавших восстанавливать Штормград. Когда знать отказалась платить за их услуги, ван Клиф основал Братство Справедливости, чьей целью было &lt;i&gt;разобрать&lt;/i&gt; Штормград по камешку.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Ele liderou os Alvanéis na reconstrução de Ventobravo. Quando os nobres se recusaram a pagar, ele fundou a Irmandade Défias para... bem, &lt;i&gt;desconstruir&lt;/i&gt; Ventobravo.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Dowodził murarzami, którzy zrekonstruowali Wichrogród, a kiedy szlachta odmówiła zapłaty, założył bractwo Nieskornych, żeby &lt;i&gt;zdekonstruować&lt;/i&gt; Wichrogród.</plPL>
    <koKR>그는 스톰윈드를 재건하는 석공 길드를 이끌었는데, 귀족들이 돈을 지불하지 않자 데피아즈단을 결성해 &lt;i&gt;오히려&lt;/i&gt; 스톰윈드를 마구 부쉈답니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Ha guidato i tagliapietre nella ricostruzione di Roccavento, e quando i nobili si sono rifiutati di pagare ha fondato la Fratellanza dei Defias per... be'... &lt;i&gt;decostruire&lt;/i&gt; la capitale.</itIT>
    <frFR>Il a dirigé les maçons lors de la reconstruction de Hurlevent, et lorsque les nobles ont refusé de payer, il a fondé la Confrérie défias pour, eh bien, &lt;i&gt;redécorer&lt;/i&gt; la ville.</frFR>
    <esMX>Comandó a los Albañiles durante la reconstrucción de Ventormenta, y cuando los nobles se negaron a pagar, fundó la Hermandad Defias para... bueno, para &lt;i&gt;destruir&lt;/i&gt; Ventormenta.</esMX>
    <esES>Lideraba a los albañiles que reconstruyeron Ventormenta, y cuando los nobles se negaron a pagarle, fundó la Hermandad Defias para, en fin, &lt;i&gt;deconstruir&lt;/i&gt; Ventormenta.</esES>
    <deDE>Er leitete die Steinmetze beim Wiederaufbau von Sturmwind, und als die Adligen nicht zahlen wollten, gründete er die Bruderschaft der Defias, um Sturmwind, nun ja, wieder &lt;i&gt;abzubauen&lt;/i&gt;.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="Combo" enumID="220" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="0dc05696-d7b6-49b3-b03b-485b2770d1f6" />
</Entity>