<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_595">
  <MasterPower>
  </MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Cult Master</enUS>
    <frFR>Maître de culte</frFR>
    <zhTW>教派宗師</zhTW>
    <zhCN>诅咒教派领袖</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Глава культа</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Mestra do Culto</ptBR>
    <plPL>Przewodniczka kultu</plPL>
    <koKR>이교도 지도자</koKR>
    <itIT>Maestra del Culto</itIT>
    <esMX>Maestra de secta</esMX>
    <esES>Maestra de secta</esES>
    <deDE>Kultmeisterin</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>Whenever one of your other minions dies, draw a card.</enUS>
    <frFR>Vous piochez une carte quand un de vos autres serviteurs meurt.</frFR>
    <zhTW>每當你其他的手下死亡，抽一張牌。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>每当你的其他随从死亡时，抽一张牌。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Когда другое ваше существо умирает, вы берете карту.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Quando um de seus outros lacaios morrer, compre um card.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Dobierz kartę za każdym razem, gdy zginie jeden z twoich stronników.</plPL>
    <koKR>나의 다른 하수인 1마리가 죽을 때마다 카드를 1장 뽑습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Quando uno degli altri tuoi servitori muore, pesca una carta.</itIT>
    <esMX>Cada vez que muere uno de tus otros esbirros, roba una carta.</esMX>
    <esES>Cuando uno de tus otros esbirros muere, roba una carta.</esES>
    <deDE>Zieht jedes Mal eine Karte, wenn einer Eurer anderen Diener stirbt.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardTextInPlay" enumID="252" type="String">
    <enUS>Cultist</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="DevState" enumID="268" type="DevState" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Raymond Swanland</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>She may be an evil cult master, but she still calls her parents once a week.</enUS>
    <zhTW>雖然她是個邪惡的教派宗師，但她還是會每個星期固定和父母聯絡。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>也许她是个邪恶的教派领袖，但是每个星期她都会和她的父母通电话。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Между прочим, даже став злобной главой культа, она по-прежнему раз в неделю звонит своим родителям.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Ela pode ser uma mestra do culto maligna, mas liga para os pais uma vez por semana.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Może i przewodzi nikczemnemu kultowi, ale i tak co tydzień dzwoni do rodziców.</plPL>
    <koKR>사악한 이교도 지도자지만 일주일에 한 번은 꼭 부모님께 전화하는 '효녀'랍니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Può anche essere la Maestra del Culto, ma deve ancora chiamare i suoi genitori una volta alla settimana.</itIT>
    <frFR>Elle a beau être à la tête d’un culte diabolique, elle appelle quand même ses parents toutes les semaines.</frFR>
    <esMX>Será una maestra de la secta maligna, sí... pero todavía llama a sus padres una vez por semana.</esMX>
    <esES>Aunque sea una maestra de secta malvada, siempre se acuerda de llamar a sus padres una vez por semana.</esES>
    <deDE>Sie mag vielleicht eine böse Kultmeisterin sein, aber sie meldet sich noch immer jede Woche bei ihren Eltern.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="TriggerVisual" enumID="32" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="eb6fb68c-f67e-4804-8096-405d33e32a6b" />
  <TriggeredPowerHistoryInfo effectIndex="0" showInHistory="False" />
</Entity>