<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_298">
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Ragnaros the Firelord</enUS>
    <frFR>Ragnaros, seigneur du feu</frFR>
    <zhTW>『炎魔』拉格納羅斯</zhTW>
    <zhCN>炎魔之王拉格纳罗斯</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Рагнарос</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Ragnaros, o Senhor do Fogo</ptBR>
    <plPL>Ragnaros Władca Ognia</plPL>
    <koKR>불의 군주 라그나로스</koKR>
    <itIT>Ragnaros</itIT>
    <esMX>Ragnaros el Señor del Fuego</esMX>
    <esES>Ragnaros, Señor del Fuego</esES>
    <deDE>Ragnaros der Feuerfürst</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="8" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="8" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="8" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="3" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>Can't Attack.  At the end of your turn, deal 8 damage to a random enemy.</enUS>
    <frFR>Ne peut pas attaquer. À la fin de votre tour, inflige 8 points de dégâts à un adversaire aléatoire.</frFR>
    <zhTW>無法攻擊。你的回合結束時，對一名隨機敵人造成8點傷害</zhTW>
    <zhCN>无法攻击，在你的回合结束时，对一个随机敌人造成8点伤害。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Не может атаковать. В конце вашего хода наносит 8 ед. урона случайному персонажу противника.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Não pode atacar. No final do seu turno, cause 8 de dano a um inimigo aleatório.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Nie może atakować. Na koniec swojej tury zadaj 8 pkt. obrażeń losowemu wrogowi.</plPL>
    <koKR>이 하수인은 적을 공격할 수 없습니다. 내 턴이 끝날 때 무작위 적에게 피해를 8 줍니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Non può attaccare. Alla fine del tuo turno, infligge 8 danni a un nemico casuale.</itIT>
    <esMX>No puede atacar. Al final de tu turno, inflige 8 de daño a un enemigo aleatorio.</esMX>
    <esES>No puede atacar. Al final de tu turno, inflige 8 p. de daño a un enemigo aleatorio.</esES>
    <deDE>Kann nicht angreifen. Fügt am Ende Eures Zuges einem zufälligen Feind 8 Schaden zu.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="DevState" enumID="268" type="DevState" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Elite" enumID="114" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Greg Staples</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>Ragnaros was summoned by the Dark Iron dwarves, who were eventually enslaved by the Firelord.  Summoning Ragnaros often doesn’t work out the way you want it to.</enUS>
    <zhTW>拉格納羅斯是被黑鐵矮人召喚出來的，但他們後來反倒被炎魔奴役。只能說，召喚拉格納羅斯通常不會達到你期望的結果。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>拉格纳罗斯是由黑铁矮人召唤出来的，而这些矮人最终也成为了火焰领主的奴隶。所以召唤拉格纳罗斯往往得不到你想要的结果。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Рагнароса призвали дворфы клана Черного Железа, и это закончилось тем, что Повелитель огня их поработил. Мораль: не призывайте Рагнароса, это может плохо кончиться.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Ragnaros foi evocado pelos anões Ferro Negro, que acabaram sendo escravizados pelo Senhor do Fogo. Evocar Ragnaros raramente funciona como você gostaria.</ptBR>
    <plPL>„CZY WIESZ, ŻE WSZYSTKO CO KOCHASZ, JEST ŁATWOPALNE?”</plPL>
    <koKR>라그나로스를 소환한 것은 검은무쇠 드워프였지만, 이들은 결국 불의 군주를 섬기는 노예가 되고 말았습니다. 이렇게 라그나로스를 소환하는 일은 원치 않는 결과를 불러오는 일이 많습니다. </koKR>
    <itIT>Ragnaros venne evocato dai Nani Ferroscuro, che furono immediatamente schiavizzati dal Signore del Fuoco. Evocare Ragnaros spesso non funziona come vorresti.</itIT>
    <frFR>Ragnaros a été invoqué par les nains sombrefers, qui au final se sont retrouvés esclaves du seigneur du feu. Invoquer Ragnaros a souvent des effets secondaires indésirables...</frFR>
    <esMX>Los enanos Hierro negro invocaron a Ragnaros, que luego terminó esclavizándolos. A menudo, Invocar al Señor del Fuego no funciona como uno espera.</esMX>
    <esES>Los enanos Hierro Negro invocaron a Ragnaros, el Señor del Fuego, pero este acabó esclavizándolos. Se ve que invocar a Ragnaros no siempre sale como uno espera.</esES>
    <deDE>Ragnaros wurde von den Dunkeleisenzwergen herbeigerufen, die schlussendlich von ihm versklavt wurden. Ihn zu beschwören hat oft nicht die gewünschten Auswirkungen.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="TriggerVisual" enumID="32" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="c43bc5ec-c7d0-4e2d-8637-5c68a33bb5d2" />
  <Power definition="36c872c7-3b2b-4a77-a4de-48ed62887235" />
  <TriggeredPowerHistoryInfo effectIndex="0" showInHistory="True" />
</Entity>