<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="NEW1_021">
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Doomsayer</enUS>
    <frFR>Auspice funeste</frFR>
    <zhTW>末日預言者</zhTW>
    <zhCN>末日预言者</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Вестник рока</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Agoureiro</ptBR>
    <plPL>Prorok zagłady</plPL>
    <koKR>파멸의 예언자</koKR>
    <itIT>Vate della Rovina</itIT>
    <esMX>Orador del sino</esMX>
    <esES>Orador del Sino</esES>
    <deDE>Untergangsverkünder</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="4" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="0" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="7" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>At the start of your turn, destroy ALL minions.</enUS>
    <frFR>Au début de votre tour, détruit TOUS les serviteurs.</frFR>
    <zhTW>在你的回合開始時，摧毀全部手下</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在你的回合开始时，消灭所有随从。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>В начале вашего хода уничтожает ВСЕХ существ.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>No início do seu turno, destrua TODOS os lacaios.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Na początku swojej tury zniszcz WSZYSTKICH stronników.</plPL>
    <koKR>내 턴이 시작될 때, &lt;b&gt;모든&lt;/b&gt; 하수인을 처치합니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>All'inizio del tuo turno, distrugge TUTTI i servitori.</itIT>
    <esMX>Al comienzo de tu turno, destruye a TODOS los esbirros.</esMX>
    <esES>Al comienzo de tu turno, destruye a todos los esbirros.</esES>
    <deDE>Vernichtet zu Beginn Eures Zuges ALLE Diener.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Alex Horley Orlandelli</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>He's almost been right so many times. He was &lt;i&gt;sure&lt;/i&gt; it was coming during the Cataclysm.</enUS>
    <zhTW>他的預言好幾次都差點成真。他&lt;b&gt;非常肯定&lt;/b&gt;的說大災變那次就是真正的末日。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>他的预言几乎都是准确的。他确信，大约会是在《大地的裂变》。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Столько раз он был близок к истине, предрекая конец света... Он был совершенно уверен, что Катаклизм уж точно положит конец всему сущему.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Ele esteve quase certo tantas vezes. Ele tinha &lt;i&gt;certeza&lt;/i&gt; que o fim do mundo chegaria no Cataclismo.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Lepiej mu idzie prorokowanie numerów na loterii.</plPL>
    <koKR>그의 예언은 가끔씩 들어맞습니다. 특히 대격변이 한창인 와중에 자신에게 파멸이 찾아올 거라는 말은 분명히 맞았습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Ha avuto quasi ragione così tante volte... durante il Cataclisma però era &lt;i&gt;sicuro&lt;/i&gt; che la rovina sarebbe arrivata.</itIT>
    <frFR>Il a toujours presque raison. Il était &lt;i&gt;certain&lt;/i&gt; que la fin du monde allait se passer pendant le cataclysme.</frFR>
    <esMX>Estuvo casi en lo cierto muchísimas veces. Estaba &lt;i&gt;seguro&lt;/i&gt; de que vendría durante el Cataclismo.</esMX>
    <esES>Después de tantos años de presagiar el fin del mundo, con el Cataclismo pensó que de verdad había llegado el momento.</esES>
    <deDE>Er hatte schon so oft beinahe recht. Er war sich &lt;i&gt;absolut sicher&lt;/i&gt;, dass es beim Kataklysmus endlich klappen würde.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="TriggerVisual" enumID="32" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="dfe6cdc8-d829-4b55-8265-516985561961" />
  <Power definition="f1931b9b-7af9-416c-9d34-fab6755f5507" />
  <TriggeredPowerHistoryInfo effectIndex="0" showInHistory="True" />
</Entity>