<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="FP1_008">
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Spectral Knight</enUS>
    <zhTW>鬼靈騎士</zhTW>
    <zhCN>鬼灵骑士</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Призрачный рыцарь</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Cavaleiro Espectral</ptBR>
    <plPL>Widmowy rycerz</plPL>
    <koKR>유령 기사</koKR>
    <itIT>Comandante Spettrale</itIT>
    <frFR>Chevalier de la mort spectral</frFR>
    <esMX>Caballero espectral</esMX>
    <esES>Caballero espectral</esES>
    <deDE>Spektraler Ritter</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="12" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="6" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>Can't be targeted by spells or Hero Powers.</enUS>
    <zhTW>無法被法術或英雄能力指定</zhTW>
    <zhCN>无法成为法术或英雄技能的目标。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Не может быть целью заклинаний и силы героя.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Não pode ser alvo de feitiços nem de Poderes Heroicos.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Nie może zostać wybrany jako cel zaklęć lub mocy specjalnych.</plPL>
    <koKR>이 하수인은 주문이나 영웅 능력의 대상으로 지정되지 않습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Non può essere il bersaglio di Magie o Poteri Eroe.</itIT>
    <frFR>Ne peut pas être la cible de sorts ou de pouvoirs héroïques.</frFR>
    <esMX>No puede ser objetivo de Hechizos o Poderes de héroe.</esMX>
    <esES>No puede ser objetivo de hechizos ni de poderes de héroe.</esES>
    <deDE>Kann nicht als Ziel von Zaubern oder Heldenfähigkeiten gewählt werden.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>What do Faerie Dragons and Spectral Knights have in common?  They both love pasta!</enUS>
    <zhTW>精靈龍跟鬼靈騎士有什麼共通點?他們都愛吃麵!</zhTW>
    <zhCN>精灵龙和鬼灵骑士有什么共同之处？它们的名字里都有“灵”字！</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Что общего у чудесных дракончиков и призрачных рыцарей? Они оба любят покушать!</ruRU>
    <ptBR>O que as Dragoletas e os Calaveiros Espectrais têm em comum? Os dois gostam de macarrão!</ptBR>
    <plPL>Co wspólnego mają baśniowe smoki i widmowi rycerze? Trudno w nich wycelować!</plPL>
    <koKR>요정용과 유령 기사의 공통점이 뭐냐고요? 음... 둘 다 파스타를 좋아한다는 거?</koKR>
    <itIT>Che cos'hanno in comune i Draghi Fatati e i Comandanti Spettrali? Entrambi adorano il sushi!</itIT>
    <frFR>Qu’ont en commun les dragons féeriques et les chevaliers de la mort spectraux ? Ils adorent les pâtes !</frFR>
    <esMX>¿Qué tienen en común los Dragones feéricos y los Caballeros espectrales? ¡Que los dos adoran los tallarines!</esMX>
    <esES>¿Qué tienen en común los dragones feéricos y los caballeros espectrales?... ¡Que les encanta merendar!</esES>
    <deDE>Wie ein echter Ritter, nur durchsichtig.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Chris Rahn</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisCard" enumID="364" type="String">
    <enUS>Unlocked by defeating Gothik the Harvester in the Military Quarter.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在軍事區擊敗『收割者』高希後解鎖。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在击败军事区的收割者戈提克后解锁。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Награда за победу над Готиком Жнецом в Военном квартале.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Desbloqueado ao derrotar Gothik, o Ceifador, no Distrito Militar.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Aby odblokować, pokonaj Gotyka Żniwiarza w Rewirze Zbrojnych.</plPL>
    <koKR>군사 지구의 영혼 착취자 고딕을 쓰러뜨려 잠금 해제</koKR>
    <itIT>Sbloccata sconfiggendo Gothik il Falciatore nell'Ala dei Combattenti.</itIT>
    <frFR>Obtenue en gagnant contre Gothik le Moissonneur dans le quartier Militaire.</frFR>
    <esMX>Desbloqueada por derrotar a Gothik el Cosechador en el Arrabal Militar.</esMX>
    <esES>Se desbloquea al derrotar a Gothik el Cosechador en el Arrabal Militar.</esES>
    <deDE>Wird durch den Sieg über Gothik den Ernter im Militärviertel freigeschaltet.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisGoldCard" enumID="365" type="String">
    <enUS>Can be crafted after defeating Gothik the Harvester in the Military Quarter.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在軍事區中擊敗『收割者』高希即可合成。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在军事区击败收割者戈提克后能够制作。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Можно создать после победы над Готиком Жнецом в Военном квартале.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Pode ser criado após derrotar Gothik, o Ceifador, no Distrito Militar.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Można wykonać po pokonaniu Gotyka Żniwiarza w Rewirze Zbrojnych.</plPL>
    <koKR>군사 지구의 영혼 수확자 고딕을 쓰러뜨린 후 제작 가능</koKR>
    <itIT>Può essere creata dopo aver sconfitto Gothik il Falciatore nell'Ala dei Combattenti.</itIT>
    <frFR>Peut être créée après avoir battu Gothik le Moissonneur dans le quartier Militaire.</frFR>
    <esMX>Se puede crear luego de derrotar a Gothik el Cosechador en el Arrabal Militar.</esMX>
    <esES>Se puede crear tras derrotar a Gothik el Cosechador en el Arrabal Militar.</esES>
    <deDE>Kann nach dem Sieg über Gothik den Ernter im Militärviertel hergestellt werden.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Power definition="043a0ebc-4626-43cc-a2ad-49a2953af429" />
</Entity>