<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="EX1_564">
  <MasterPower>111ce0c3-f379-4a32-b181-955d962aa42a</MasterPower>
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Faceless Manipulator</enUS>
    <frFR>Manipulateur sans-visage</frFR>
    <zhTW>無面操縱者</zhTW>
    <zhCN>无面操纵者</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Безликий манипулятор</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Manipulador Sem-rosto</ptBR>
    <plPL>Beztwarzowy manipulator</plPL>
    <koKR>얼굴 없는 배후자</koKR>
    <itIT>Senzavolto Mutante</itIT>
    <esMX>Manipulador ignoto</esMX>
    <esES>Manipulador ignoto</esES>
    <deDE>Gesichtsloser Manipulator</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="4" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="5" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Faction" enumID="201" type="Faction" value="3" />
  <Tag name="AttackVisualType" enumID="251" type="AttackVisualType" value="9" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Battlecry:&lt;/b&gt; Choose a minion and become a copy of it.</enUS>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Cri de guerre :&lt;/b&gt; choisit un serviteur et en devient la copie conforme.</frFR>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;戰吼:&lt;/b&gt;選擇一個手下並成為它的複製品</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;战吼：&lt;/b&gt;选择一个随从，成为它的复制。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Боевой клич:&lt;/b&gt; становится копией выбранного существа.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Grito de Guerra:&lt;/b&gt; Escolha um lacaio e torne-se uma cópia dele.</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Okrzyk bojowy:&lt;/b&gt; Wybierz stronnika i stań się jego kopią.</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;전투의 함성:&lt;/b&gt; 선택한 하수인으로 변신합니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Grido di Battaglia:&lt;/b&gt; scegli un altro servitore, il Senzavolto Mutante diventa una sua copia.</itIT>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla:&lt;/b&gt; elige un esbirro y se convierte en una copia de él.</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Grito de batalla:&lt;/b&gt; Elige a un esbirro y se convierte en una copia de este.</esES>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Kampfschrei:&lt;/b&gt; Wählt einen Diener aus, um Gesichtsloser Manipulator in eine Kopie desselben zu verwandeln.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="TargetingArrowText" enumID="325" type="String">
    <enUS>Become a copy of a minion.</enUS>
    <frFR>Devient une copie d’un serviteur.</frFR>
    <zhTW>複製一個手下。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>成为一个随从的复制。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Превратить в копию существа</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Torne-se uma cópia de um lacaio.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Wybierz stronnika do skopiowania.</plPL>
    <koKR>선택한 하수인으로 변신</koKR>
    <itIT>Diventa la copia di un servitore.</itIT>
    <esMX>Se convierte en una copia de un esbirro.</esMX>
    <esES>Se convierte en una copia de un esbirro.</esES>
    <deDE>Wird zur Kopie eines Dieners.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Raymond Swanland</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>The Faceless Ones are servants of Yogg-Saron, and they feed on fear. Right now they are feeding on your fear of accidentally disenchanting all your good cards.</enUS>
    <zhTW>無面者是尤格薩倫的僕人，它們以恐懼為食。現在它們正在吞食你害怕不小心把好牌全分解掉的恐懼。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>作为尤格萨隆的仆从，无面者们以人们的恐惧为食，而现在他们的菜谱中包括你对“不小心把好牌分解掉”的担心和忧虑。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Безликие – слуги Йогг-Сарона, и они питаются страхом. Вот прямо сейчас они смакуют ваш страх случайно распылить все хорошие карты.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Os Sem-rosto são servos de Yogg-Saron e eles se alimentam de medo. Neste momento, eles estão se alimentando do seu medo de desencantar acidentalmente todos os cards bons.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Beztwarzowi są sługami Yogg-Sarona i żywią się strachem. Obecnie żywią się twoim strachem przed przypadkowym odczarowaniem najlepszych kart.</plPL>
    <koKR>얼굴 없는 자들은 공포를 먹고 사는 요그사론의 하수인입니다. 지금도 좋은 카드들을 실수로 마력 추출해버리면 어쩌나 걱정하고 있는 당신의 공포를 먹고 있죠.</koKR>
    <itIT>I Senzavolto sono i servitori di Yogg-Saron e si nutrono della paura. Al momento si stanno nutrendo della tua paura di disincantare distrattamente tutte le tue carte utili.</itIT>
    <frFR>Les sans-visages sont les serviteurs de Yogg-Saron et ils se nourrissent de la peur. En ce moment, celui-ci se nourrit de votre peur de désenchanter toutes vos bonnes cartes par accident.</frFR>
    <esMX>Los ignotos son los sirvientes de Yogg-Saron y se alimentan del miedo. En este momento, se están alimentando de tu miedo de desencantar tus mejores cartas por error.</esMX>
    <esES>Los manipuladores ignotos son sirvientes de Yogg-Saron y se alimentan de tu miedo. Ahora mismo se está alimentando de tu miedo a desencantar una carta buena por accidente.</esES>
    <deDE>Die Gesichtslosen sind die Diener Yogg-Sarons und ernähren sich von Angst. Im Augenblick laben sie sich an Eurer Angst davor, aus Versehen all Eure guten Karten zu entzaubern.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Battlecry" enumID="218" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="111ce0c3-f379-4a32-b181-955d962aa42a">
    <PlayRequirement reqID="22" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="1" param="" />
    <PlayRequirement reqID="9" param="" />
  </Power>
</Entity>