<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Entity version="2" CardID="FP1_005">
  <Tag name="CardName" enumID="185" type="String">
    <enUS>Shade of Naxxramas</enUS>
    <zhTW>納克薩瑪斯幻影</zhTW>
    <zhCN>纳克萨玛斯之影</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Тень Наксрамаса</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Vulto de Naxxramas</ptBR>
    <plPL>Cień z Naxxramas</plPL>
    <koKR>낙스라마스의 망령</koKR>
    <itIT>Ombra di Naxxramas</itIT>
    <frFR>Ombre de Naxxramas</frFR>
    <esMX>Sombra de Naxxramas</esMX>
    <esES>Sombra de Naxxramas</esES>
    <deDE>Naxxramasschemen</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="Collectible" enumID="321" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="CardSet" enumID="183" type="CardSet" value="12" />
  <Tag name="Rarity" enumID="203" type="Rarity" value="4" />
  <Tag name="CardType" enumID="202" type="CardType" value="4" />
  <Tag name="Cost" enumID="48" type="Number" value="3" />
  <Tag name="Atk" enumID="47" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="Health" enumID="45" type="Number" value="2" />
  <Tag name="CardTextInHand" enumID="184" type="String">
    <enUS>&lt;b&gt;Stealth.&lt;/b&gt; At the start of your turn, gain +1/+1.</enUS>
    <zhTW>&lt;b&gt;潛行&lt;/b&gt;。在你回合開始時，獲得+1/+1</zhTW>
    <zhCN>&lt;b&gt;潜行。&lt;/b&gt;在你的回合开始时，获得+1/+1。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>&lt;b&gt;Маскировка.&lt;/b&gt; В начале вашего хода получает +1/+1.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>&lt;b&gt;Furtividade.&lt;/b&gt; No início do seu turno, receba +1/+1.</ptBR>
    <plPL>&lt;b&gt;Ukrycie.&lt;/b&gt; Otrzymuje +1/+1 na początku twojej tury.</plPL>
    <koKR>&lt;b&gt;은신.&lt;/b&gt; 내 턴이 시작될 때, +1/+1을 얻습니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>&lt;b&gt;Furtività&lt;/b&gt;. All'inizio del tuo turno, ottiene +1/+1.</itIT>
    <frFR>&lt;b&gt;Camouflage.&lt;/b&gt; Gagne +1/+1 au début de votre tour.</frFR>
    <esMX>&lt;b&gt;Sigilo.&lt;/b&gt; Al comienzo de tu turno, obtiene +1/+1.</esMX>
    <esES>&lt;b&gt;Sigilo.&lt;/b&gt; Al comienzo de tu turno, obtiene +1/+1.</esES>
    <deDE>&lt;b&gt;Verstohlenheit&lt;/b&gt;. Erhält zu Beginn Eures Zuges +1/+1.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="EnchantmentBirthVisual" enumID="330" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="EnchantmentIdleVisual" enumID="331" type="EnchantmentVisualType" value="0" />
  <Tag name="FlavorText" enumID="351" type="String">
    <enUS>The Shades of Naxxramas &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; the living. They even have a slur they use to refer them: &lt;i&gt;Livers&lt;/i&gt;.</enUS>
    <zhTW>納克薩瑪斯幻影痛恨生者。他們非得把生者弄死，否則不會罷休。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>纳克萨玛斯之影真的很讨厌活的东西。在他们看来，人类和兽人确实有所区别，就像蛆虫和老鼠的区别一样。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Тени Наксрамаса ненавидят все живое. Они даже кличку смертным придумали – «живчики».</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Os Vultos de Naxxramas &lt;i&gt;odeiam&lt;/i&gt; os vivos. Eles têm até um termo pejorativo que usam para mencioná-los: &lt;i&gt;Viventes&lt;/i&gt;.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Paradoksalnie, wszystkie cienie boją się ciemności. W końcu nie mogą istnieć bez odrobiny światła.</plPL>
    <koKR>전설도 아니면서 그룰보다 높은 생존력을 자랑합니다.</koKR>
    <itIT>Le Ombre di Naxxramas &lt;i&gt;odiano&lt;/i&gt; i vivi. Hanno perfino coniato un termine dispregiativo per riferirsi a essi: &lt;i&gt;vividi&lt;/i&gt;.</itIT>
    <frFR>Regardez vers la lumière, les ombres resteront derrière vous !</frFR>
    <esMX>Dicen que en Naxxramas faltan 50 sombras porque se fueron con Grey.</esMX>
    <esES>Las sombras de Naxxramas &lt;i&gt;odian&lt;/i&gt; a los vivos. Hasta tienen un insulto propio para ellos: &lt;i&gt;vivoncios&lt;/i&gt;.</esES>
    <deDE>Die Schemen von Naxxramas sind nicht sehr einfallsreiche Kämpfer. Man könnte fast sagen, sie gehen nach Schema vor.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="ArtistName" enumID="342" type="String">
    <enUS>Ittoku Seta</enUS>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisCard" enumID="364" type="String">
    <enUS>Unlocked by defeating Kel'Thuzad in the Frostwyrm Lair.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在冰霜巨龍巢穴擊敗科爾蘇加德後解鎖。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在击败冰龙巢穴的克尔苏加德后解锁。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Награда за победу над Кел'Тузадом в Логове ледяного змея.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Desbloqueado ao derrotar Kel'thuzad no Covil da Serpe Gélida.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Aby odblokować, pokonaj Kel'Thuzada w Legowisku Żmija Mrozu.</plPL>
    <koKR>서리고룡 둥지의 켈투자드를 쓰러뜨려 잠금 해제</koKR>
    <itIT>Sbloccata sconfiggendo Kel'Thuzad nell'Antro del Gelo.</itIT>
    <frFR>Obtenue en gagnant contre Kel’Thuzad dans l’antre du Wyrm de givre.</frFR>
    <esMX>Desbloqueada por derrotar a Kel'Thuzad en la Guarida de la Vermis.</esMX>
    <esES>Se desbloquea al derrotar a Kel'Thuzad en la Guarida de la Vermis.</esES>
    <deDE>Wird durch den Sieg über Kel'Thuzad in der Spitze der Nekropole freigeschaltet.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="HowToGetThisGoldCard" enumID="365" type="String">
    <enUS>Can be crafted after defeating Kel'Thuzad in the Frostwyrm Lair.</enUS>
    <zhTW>在冰霜巨龍巢穴中擊敗科爾蘇加德即可合成。</zhTW>
    <zhCN>在冰龙巢穴击败克尔苏加德后能够制作。</zhCN>
    <ruRU>Можно создать после победы над Кел'Тузадом в Логове ледяного змея.</ruRU>
    <ptBR>Pode ser criado após derrotar Kel'thuzad no Covil da Serpe Gélida.</ptBR>
    <plPL>Można wykonać po pokonaniu Kel'Thuzada w Legowisku Żmija Mrozu.</plPL>
    <koKR>서리고룡 둥지의 켈투자드를 쓰러뜨린 후 제작 가능</koKR>
    <itIT>Può essere creata dopo aver sconfitto Kel'Thuzad nell'Antro del Gelo.</itIT>
    <frFR>Peut être créée après avoir battu Kel’Thuzad dans l’antre du Wyrm de givre.</frFR>
    <esMX>Se puede crear luego de derrotar a Kel'Thuzad en la Guarida de la Vermis.</esMX>
    <esES>Se puede crear tras derrotar a Kel'Thuzad en la Guarida de la Vermis.</esES>
    <deDE>Kann nach dem Sieg über Kel'Thuzad in der Spitze der Nekropole hergestellt werden.</deDE>
  </Tag>
  <Tag name="TriggerVisual" enumID="32" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Tag name="Stealth" enumID="191" type="Bool" value="1" />
  <Power definition="aa8deb54-9ba5-4322-8adb-56a1e18a139a" />
  <Power definition="5b2f9dd8-e228-496a-a2a8-f68c9e011cca" />
  <TriggeredPowerHistoryInfo effectIndex="0" showInHistory="False" />
</Entity>